Ending
Good Morning
Good morning.
Oh!
You've got to be kidding me.
Here you go.
Good morning.
Laughter.
Hey, guys.
Yoo-hoo!
Wow.
Wow, wow, that looks good.
Oh, my gosh.
Looks delicious.
A little more.
Kuromi just now.
She said, "Spamen bread hasn't come yet!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
So cool!
The sweet potatoes are good too.
This is really good too
Itchy is recommended
But already
This is all you've got?
Yesterday, about four packs.
That's a lot of food.
I ate a lot.
It's not good.
It was all messed up.
I don't know what to do.
It's so messy.
I love it.
I love the red dress.
Bon appétit!
Greetings
To Tsubamen bread
Greetings to Tsubamen bread
Bon appétit!
I got the red coat!
Eh, it's not so beautiful.
Oh well...
I can't do it, but...
Same thing.
I know.
Oh, yeah.
Let's do it one more time.
Just to be hugged
While confiding my sorrows
But even now, all this time
You love me more than I love you
Wide boat
Thank you for all your hard work.
Yay!
Oh, I loved those things!
Yay!!!
Thank you for the show yesterday.
Please start from the rehearsal today as well.
Thank you very much.
I'll have the remaining seven of you fill in the flat.
Today's Nagoya venue is
Unlike other venues
there is a hanamichi (flower aisle).
I'll be on the aisle today.
I'm making arrangements now.
Close to the customers
I'm going to be close to the customers.
so that we can go.
We are all working on it.
Now, this rehearsal will be a routine rehearsal.
When we do a performance and the copper wire is hard to see because of the lighting,
When we have a performance and the lighting is not good enough to see the copper wire, the members ask if we can change the lighting a little more here and there,
We have been making changes every time we have a review meeting, but this is just a routine check.
Thank you very much.
There is a camera here.
I shouldn't have taken this.
Oh, it's okay.
Thank you.
What did you eat?
Did you take a picture?
I'm familiar with the controls.
Oh, that's good.
Eat up.
It's an hour and a half before you have to change.
I've got plenty of time.
Okay, bye.
You said you wouldn't do it on camera.
I really don't.
Hide it.
You scared me.
What was the point of your hair today?
It's like a...
It's like a braid.
It's definitely braided.
I like it. It looks cool.
It's a little split here.
That's right.
You look good with it split.
It's cute.
I'm so happy.
You and Kaede are wearing the same siblings today.
So cute!
It looks good on you with your hair up.
I'm so glad.
Your face is so cute
I love the little one!
I put my hair in side-tails to match Hane-san's.
You parted your bangs today.
I parted my bangs.
That's unusual.
It's rare.
Parted.
Good luck.
Yes, sir.
Okay, then.
What do you think of today's haircut?
You and Lilia are matching today.
You're all matching.
Yes, that's right.
Cute.
You can be all over the place.
What a nice touch.
Cute.
I'll go then.
I'm not really in demand.
It's delicious.
Everyone's gone to make-up.
There's no one in the dressing room now.
Delicious!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. What is the point of today's hairstyle?
Today's hair point is my forehead.
Cute.
I'll drink soup.
I can drink soup. It's cute.
Have you eaten? I ate it.
I did.
Was it good?
Swallow bread.
It was really good.It was so delicious.
It was delicious.
Subscribe to our channel!
Yes, so this is the last of the single voice of the tour already!
We will see you in Tokyo for the next two weeks or so.
We really want to give it our all today and make the audience excited.
Let's do our best so that we can give it our all today, and at the same time, we will be the most impatient of all!
I'll be there!
Here we go! Let's go!
No! You!
You! Se-no!
Boo-boo! Thank you! Smile, JAM's in trouble!
Well, open season!
Thanks for your hard work!
I'll hurry up.
The secret of the earpiece
Can you see it?
It's got your name written on it.
It's on that side.
It's written on that side.
That's the secret of the earpiece.
Thank you very much.
To the new world
I'm doing it too
Okay, let's go.
And Mike.
Mike, the manager.
You took my schedule, you.
No, my mouth is open.
That's a good thing.
Hmm?
What?
What are you talking about?
Can you feel my touch?
No, I don't think so.
What was that?
There's no nerve in the tooth.
Oh, but on the surface...
You wouldn't know it if it rattled.
I touched it.
Okay, let's see the liner board.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
You've made me a senior.
What's the other way around?
I'm so nervous.
I was afraid I'd make a mistake.
I was afraid I'd make a mistake, and she said, "Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
It's going to be okay.
Let's go for it.
Aya's style
I'll shake it off.
Aya's face, not at all.
She doesn't dance.
Really?
But you don't mind?
I'm totally fine.
I'm scared.
Let's eat.
Let's try it.
That's it.
Cheer for me!
Cheer for us!
Oh-kun, you won!
Okun, I lost...
Okun, I did it with my victory.
Oh-kun, I won... ★ Oh-kun, I won... ★
Honey.
I'm going to sing now.
I'm going to rap and sing from now on
Honey
I'm going to take honey for my throat and do my best.
I can hear the audience.
Sorry! No honking!
Hand me that. That's it.
Oh! Motorcycle!
Motorcycle.
Ooh! I wish I was out.
Yes, sir.
Let's go!
Hold on.
Sorry.
Wait for me!
I already thought it was makeup.
I said sorry.
No now.
Huh.
I've become such a cocky junior!
What's wrong with you?
It's fine.
That's fine.
I'm off.
Okay. Bye!
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, thank you very much.
How was it?
Thank you for your hard work.
You made me laugh.
Yay!
Thanks for your hard work!
Meow!
Meow meow meow
Thank you for your hard work
thank you
Thank you
Thank you.
Wait a minute, it's just Ms. Carrie, so it's not...
Vikings!
We fought.
Cute.
Guys, together.
All right.
Close, close, close.
It's close.
What?
I'm Necky Heart.
Salt kitteh.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy!
Aya took this picture for me.
Another successful year, pro nori first Access!
Thank you so much!
Oh, Aya-chan!
Aya-chan
Oh, water
Matching!
All sorts of things.
Matching
Ma-chan
Matching.
Matching
Hey, Mom.
They're always together.
Always together.
That's when the yakubo's not around.
Oh, you're a woman of convenience.
Hey, Mom.
I made a video.
It's delicious.
I'm so happy for you.
We're all eating it.
Oh, what was that?
Thank you for coming.Thank you for coming.
You're gonna make this face, right?
It's okay.
Oh, my God, I'm so sick.
Oh, man.
One more time, one more time.
LOL!
This is what you make.
Good luck. I'll be watching.
See you soon.
I'll be watching as a fan.
See you later.